[
    {
        "front": "はなす",
        "back": "話す \nTo speak/talk",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "はなし",
        "back": "話 \nStory",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "よむ",
        "back": "読む \nTo read",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "どくしょ",
        "back": "読書 \nReading books",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "にほんご",
        "back": "日本語 \nJapanese language",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうごくご",
        "back": "中国語 \nChinese language",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "みち",
        "back": "道 \nStreet, road, way",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "あいだ",
        "back": "間 \nbetween",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "じかん",
        "back": "時間 \nTime",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "いちねんかん",
        "back": "一年間 \n(for) a year",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "きく",
        "back": "聞く \nTo listen to",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "きこえる",
        "back": "聞こえる \nCan be heard",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんぶん",
        "back": "新聞 \nNewspaper",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "かう",
        "back": "買う \nTo buy",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "やすむ",
        "back": "休む \nTo rest",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "やすみ",
        "back": "休み \nHoliday",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "とき",
        "back": "時 \nTime, when",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "よじ",
        "back": "4 時 \n4 o’clock",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "いちじかん",
        "back": "1 時間 \nOne hour",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "いつしゅうかん",
        "back": "1 週間 \nOne week",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "らいしゅう",
        "back": "来週 \nNext week",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "せんしゅう",
        "back": "先週 \nLast week",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "こんしゅう",
        "back": "今週 \nThis week",
        "chapter": "N5 K10"
    }
]